Coming up:
即将到来：
Why is Murr shaking things up?
为什么 Murr 要改变现状？
You're not going to be scared at all
if it does anything, right?
如果它做任何事情，你根本不会害怕，对吧？
What's got Joe striking a pose?
是什么让 Joe 摆出姿势？
[camera snap]
[相机抓拍]
And which losing Joker
won't be able to zip it
而哪个输了的小丑将无法拉上拉链
in tonight's outspoken punishment?
在今晚直言不讳的惩罚中？
Sorry, do you have a question?
对不起，您有问题吗？
Prepare for something amazing!
准备好迎接精彩瞬间吧！
Hey, mustache, what's up?
嘿，小胡子，怎么了？
I want my mommy!
我要我的妈妈！
I will never forgive you!
我永远不会原谅你！
Larry!
拉里！
[Murr] Like a bosssssss!
[喃喃自语]就像一个老板一样！
We're here at my favorite
theme park in the world:
我们来到了世界上我最喜欢的主题公园：
Universal Orlando Resort, working
奥兰多环球影城度假村 （Universal Orlando Resort），正在运营
on their brand new Fast &
Furious Supercharged ride.
在他们全新的速度与激情增压骑行中。
While posing as employees, we're
going to have to do and say
在冒充员工时，我们将不得不做和说
whatever the other guys
tell us to.
其他人告诉我们做什么。
And today, every single refusal
而今天，每一次拒绝
counts as a thumbs down.
算作竖起大拇指。
Thumbs downs are going
to come fast and furious.
大拇指反对会来得又快又猛。
I feel like I'm hanging out in
Dom Toretto's garage.
我感觉自己就像在 Dom Toretto 的车库里闲逛。
We are big Fast & Furious
fans here. Big.
我们是这里的大速度与激情粉丝。大。
[Sal] If you're here, you
know about the family.
[萨尔]如果你在这里，你就会了解这个家庭。
And the family's ride or die.
而这个家庭要么生死。
Always ride or die.
永远骑车或死亡。
So, let's test how "ride
or die" people are.
那么，让我们测试一下人们的 “ride or die” 是如何的。
Excuse me.
对不起。
I'm here to find out how
"ride or die" are you?
我来这里是为了了解你有多 “ride or die” ？
Where you guys from?
你们来自哪里？
Ohh! That's ride or die!
哦！那就是 ride or die！
Leprechauns are ride or die.
妖精要么骑要么死。
You know what's lep...
你知道什么是 lep......
You know what's ride or die?
你知道什么是 ride or die吗？
Leprechauns.
Leprechauns are ride or die.
妖精。妖精要么骑要么死。
[vocalizes a stereotypical Irish tune] right?
[唱出刻板的爱尔兰曲调]对吧？
So I see you have bangs coming
out of the front of your cap there?
所以我看到你的帽子前面有刘海吗？
You got sunglasses indoors.
你在室内有太阳镜。
[Q clicks tongue] Like myself.
[Q 咔嚓舌头]就像我自己一样。
That's a double ride
or die, right there.
那是双倍骑行或死亡，就在那里。
You got a "Clark Kent curl" going.
你有一个 “克拉克肯特卷曲” 正在进行。
Do i? -[Sal] Yeah.
-Wish I had those muscles.
是吗？-[Sal] 是的。-希望我有那些肌肉。
You know? On top of me.
你知道的？在我之上。
[awkward silence]
[尴尬的沉默]
I wish I had the cape.
我希望我有那件斗篷。
How you doing? You guys
having fun today?
你好吗？你们今天玩得开心吗？
Say to the girl:
"Are you with him?"
对女孩说：“你和他在一起吗？
Are you with him?
你和他在一起吗？
"Seriously?!"
“真的？！”
What are you, is the machine
okay? You checking the machine?
你是什么，机器还好吗？你检查机器吗？
You having a good time?
-Yeah.
你玩得开心吗？-是的。
"You would look great
with a different wig on".
“戴上不同的假发会很棒”。
Hmm.
嗯。
[Murr laughing] Oh no! No, no!
[Murr 笑]哦不！不 不！
Q, don't you dare!
Q，你不敢！
Hair's up, looking great!
头发竖起来，看起来很棒！
Enjoy the ride.
-I will.
享受旅程。-我会的。
That's my friend, Q: The Gentleman.
那是我的朋友，Q：The Gentleman。
[Joe] Alright, buddy.
[乔]好吧，伙计。
Tap this tall kid on the
back. Here you go.
轻拍这个高个子孩子的背。给你。
Excuse me, sir?
对不起，先生？
"Yeah, the nerds, they go
in the other part of the park."
“是的，书们，他们去公园的另一边。”
Three thumbs down?
-That's three in a row.
三个大拇指朝下？- 那是连续三个。
Gunk out!
出炉！
Sal, try and scare people.
萨尔，试着吓唬人。
You guys Fast?
你们快吗？
Yeah, yeah.
是的。
Get right in people's faces.
直面人们的脸。
You Fast, bro?
你快吗，兄弟？
What?
-Are you fast?
什么？- 你快吗？
You Furious, bro?
你愤怒了，兄弟？
[Q] "You single, bro?"
[Q] “你单身吗，兄弟？”
[laughing] Alright.
[笑]好。
Are you guys from
"outside brown"?
你们是来自“外棕色”的吗？
Where you guys
coming in from?
你们从哪里来？
You guys from "outside brown"?
你们是 “outside brown” 的家伙吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Outside Brown? Great area.
在布朗之外？很棒的区域。
Had some good times
in Outside Brown.
在 Outside Brown 度过了一段美好的时光。
London? Yeah.
伦敦？是的。
[Murr] "Right outside brown"?
-Right outside brown?
[喃喃自语]“就在棕色外面”？-就在棕色外面？
It's also unclear to me.
我也不清楚。
Excuse me, sir. I'd love to talk to you,
but they don't let me talk to the animals.
对不起，先生。我很想和你谈谈，但他们不允许我和动物们说话。
Yeah.
是的。
I would love to talk
to you sir, but, uh...
我很想和你谈谈，先生，但是，呃......
You got to keep the
line going, so...
你必须保持排队，所以......
[Murr] That's #2.
[喃喃自语]那是 #2。
[Murr] Alright, Joe.
[喃喃自语]好的，乔。
Just go up to anybody in
line and just be like
只要走到排队的任何人面前，就像
"You like these, uh, Fast and
the Furious movies"?
“你喜欢这些，呃，《速度与激情》电影”？
You like these Fast and
the Furious movies"?
你喜欢这些《速度与激情》电影“吗？
"I had one of the best dates
of my life at these."
“我在这些地方度过了我一生中最美好的约会之一。”
I had one of the best dates
of my life at one of these.
我在其中之一度过了我一生中最美好的约会之一。
[Q] "Kissed my first sister"
[Q] “亲吻了我的第一个姐姐”
[stammers]
[结结巴巴]
Kissed my first sister
at that one.
在那个时候亲吻了我的第一个姐姐。
He said it!
他说了！
[Murr] Alright, Joe.
[喃喃自语]好的，乔。
Behind you. The guy with
the straw hat?
在你身后。那个戴草帽的家伙？
You been on this before?
This ride?
你以前也上过这个吗？这次骑行？
No.
不。
I'm not sure if your head's
going to fit on the ride.
我不确定你的头是否适合骑行。
I'm not sure...
我不确定。。。
I'm not sure if your, uh...
我不确定你的，呃......
I'm not sure if your head's
going to fit on it.
我不确定你的头是否能装上它。
The dome.
圆顶。
I can't believe it!
我真不敢相信！
You're going to be alright.
Get in there!
你会没事的。进去！
Joey! Wow!
乔伊！哇！
[Sal] Joe, Joe Joe Joe.
[萨尔]乔，乔乔乔。
Grab a family. Grab a family.
抓住一个家庭。抓住一个家庭。
This is your family, you guys?
这是你们的家人，你们吗？
"You guys want to cut the line?"
“你们想插队吗？”
You guys want to cut the line?
你们想插队吗？
Four of yous? Yeah? Come on.
你们四个人？是的？加油。
Come with me this way.
跟我走这边。
[Sal] Joe, Joe. Lead them to an exit door
[萨尔]乔，乔。把他们带到出口门
and just close the door on them.
然后就关上门给他们。
Shut them out of the ride!
把他们拒之门外！
Come on, keep up.
来吧，跟上。
You guys are all better than
the other families, so...
你们都比其他家族强，所以......
Right? Yeah. You think so.
右？是的。你这么认为。
Thank you. Pardon.
谢谢。赦。
[Murr] Cut in line.
-Yeah, cutting the line. Sorry.
[喃喃自语]切成一行。- 是的，剪线。不好意思。
Special family, guys.
Coming through.
特别的家庭，伙计们。借过。
[Murr] Go right through
there. Go right through.
[喃喃自语]直接穿过那里。直接通过。
Right out. Yeah, right through.
马上。是的，一直到。
I'll hold it for you.
There you go.
我替你拿着。给你。
Yeah. We don't reward,
uh, cheaters.
是的。我们不奖励，呃，作弊者。
[metal door slams]
[金属门关上]
[Murr squealing] Oh my god!
[喃喃自语]哦，我的上帝！
[Murr] Alright. Let's bring that
family to the front of the line for real.
[喃喃自语]好。让我们真正地将那个家庭带到队伍的最前面。
[Q] Just go up to random
park-goers, buddy
[Q] 随便去找公园的游客就好了，伙计
Write down what people are wearing.
写下人们的穿着。
Mumble it under your
breath as you write it.
在你写的时候低声喃喃自语。
Huh. Red bandana.
哼。红色头巾。
Floral top.
花卉上衣。
Slightly see-through.
略微透明。
Slight mustache.
轻微的小胡子。
[Q] No, no, Joe. "I was talking
to her."
[Q] 不，不，Joe。“我刚才在和她说话。”
Bam!
砰！
[Murr] Q... Q did it in season 1.
[Murr] Q...Q 在第 1 季做到了。
Your turn now! Your turn now!
现在轮到你了！现在轮到你了！
[mumbles] Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, that's right.
[喃喃自语]是的，没错。是的，没错。
That's right.
没错。
Joey!
乔伊！
Slight mustache. You thought
I was talking to you.
轻微的小胡子。你以为我在和你说话。
Yeah, that checks out.
是的，这很正常。
[Q, Murr, Sal cheering]
[Q、Murr、Sal 欢呼]
[Q] It feels so good!
[Q] 感觉真好！
[Joe] Make sure these people know
how intense this ride is.
[乔]确保这些人知道这次骑行的强度有多大。
Especially the children.
尤其是孩子们。
Do you... uh... the ride
is a little intense.
是吗。。。呃。。。骑行有点紧张。
You have? Have they been
on it, though?
你有？不过，他们上过吗？
[Joe] Okay. So you know
it goes like this.
[乔]好。所以你知道它是这样的。
Murr, start simulating
the ride with him.
Murr，开始和他一起模拟骑行。
Really, you're not going to be scared?
-[Q] Got to do more than that, buddy.
真的，你不会害怕吗？-[Q] 得做更多的事情，伙计。
You're not going to be scared at all
if it does anything, right?
如果它做任何事情，你根本不会害怕，对吧？
Not at all? The ride
does a lot of this, too.
一点也不？该游乐设施也做了很多事情。
With Vin Diesel...
-[Joe] You might lose your hat.
和 Vin Diesel 一起... -[Joe] 你可能会丢掉你的帽子。
You know, you might lose
the hat also.
你知道，你也可能失去这顶帽子。
It, you see, it does all that.
你看，它做到了这一切。
You're going to be okay, right?
You're going to be a big man?
你会没事的，对吧？你会成为一个大男人吗？
Go one more time, one more
time! Go in hard!
再来一次，再来一次！努力进去！
You going to be okay?
You going to... -Yup.
你会没事的吗？你要...-是的。
Go have fun with Fast
& Furious!
快来和Fast & Furious一起玩吧！
[Joe] There's a fella
here to your right.
[乔]你右边有个家伙。
"Does this one speak English?"
“这个会说英语吗？”
Oh, come on.
拜托。
[Q] Dude!
[Q] 伙计！
[Q] Alright. See the teenager
with no sleeves and, uh, blonde hair?
[Q] 好的。看到那个没有袖子、金发的少年了吗？
Yeah. Uh, yes.
Up here? Yeah.
是的。呃，是的。在这儿？是的。
Just ask him if he
needs to "go to potty".
问他是否需要 “去如厕”。
[quietly] Come on.
[悄悄地]加油。
You need to go potty?
你需要上厕所吗？
No? Great. Okay.
不？伟大。好。
"Are you sure?"
“你确定吗？”
Are you sure?
是否确定？
Because, don't ask me
five minutes later.
因为，不要在五分钟后问我。
"When was the last
time you pottied?"
“你上次上厕所是什么时候？”
When's the last time
you pottied?
你上一次上厕所是什么时候？
[Joe] 1 or 2?
-[laughing] "One or two?"
[Joe] 1 还是 2？-[笑]“一两个？
[Murr] Which one was it?
[喃喃自语]是哪一个？
"How'd you get in here
with those pythons"?
“你是怎么带着那些蟒蛇进来的”？
"They let you into the park
with those garden snakes?"
“他们让你和那些花园蛇一起进公园？”
This is a "Lose-A-Palooza"?
这是“Lose-A-Palooza”？
"Lose-A-Palooza".
-That's also Murray's New Year's Eve party.
“Lose-A-Palooza”。- 这也是 Murray 的除夕派对。
"How many people in
your party, sir?"
“先生，您一行有多少人？”
How many people are in your party?
-Two.
你的队伍里有多少人？-二。
It's just the two of you?
-Yeah.
就你们两个人？-是的。
It's just you and your daughter?
-Yeah.
只有你和你的女儿？-是的。
"She seems intolerable."
“她似乎无法忍受。”
Matt <3 Ali
马特 <3 阿里
How many, how many people
are in your party? -Two.
你的队伍有多少人？-二。
It's just you and your daughter?
-Yeah.
只有你和你的女儿？-是的。
"She seems intolerable."
“她似乎无法忍受。”
Oh, wow!
哦，哇！
I got to tell you.
Your daughter seems...
我得告诉你。你的女儿看起来......
adorable.
-Oh, thank you.
可爱。-谢谢。
[Sal] Another loss!
[萨尔]又一次失利！
M-M-My turn was fast.
And I am furious.
M-M-轮到我的时候很快。我很生气。
All the guys got dinged up, but Murr
and Q are in the fast lane to Loserville.
所有的人都被搞砸了，但 Murr 和 Q 正处于通往 Loserville 的快车道上。
Today we're in the park,
taking photos of strangers
今天我们在公园里，为陌生人拍照
and then asking them their permission
然后征求他们的许可
to post them on our personal
Instagram accounts.
将它们发布到我们的个人 Instagram 帐户上。
The catch is, the other guys
will be providing
问题是，其他人将提供
and awkward caption that
has to go along
和尴尬的标题，这不得不配合
with that photo.
与那张照片。
If the stranger doesn't let
you post the picture
如果陌生人不让你发布照片
and that caption, you lose.
而那个标题，你输了。
And, if you lose, you have to
post an embarrasing
而且，如果你输了，你必须发布一个尴尬的
selfie using that same caption.
使用相同标题的自拍。
[all grimacing] Cheeeese.
[全都做了个鬼脸]Cheeeese 的。
[Joe] This gentleman
looks very photogenic.
[乔]这位绅士看起来非常上镜。
[Q] He's got the "jorts".
[Joe] Oh, he's rocking "jorts".
Get the jorts in!
[Q] 他有 “jorts”。[乔]哦，他在摇摆 “jorts”。快进去吧！
[camera snap]
[相机抓拍]
[Q] Yeah, there they are.
[Murr] Yeah, there's the jorts.
[Q] 是的，他们在那里。[喃喃自语]是的，有 Jorts。
[Q] Do you need use to even
tell you what it's going to be, or...?
[Q] 你是否需要告诉你它会是什么，或者......？
[Q] Okay. Sal, uh...
[Q] 好的。萨尔，呃......
Go ahead and put, uh,
"Jorts for days".
去吧，呃，“Jorts for days”。
For anybody at home
that doesn't know
对于任何在家中不知道的人
"Jorts" are jeans, shorts...
“Jorts”是牛仔裤、短裤......
[Q and Joe together] Jorts.
[Q 和 Joe 在一起]乔茨。
[Joe] Uh, hashtag "who wears jort jorts".
[乔]呃，标签“谁穿着 jort jorts”。
Touché.
Hashtag "he wears jort jorts".
标签 “he wears jorts jorts”。
Hashtag "God bless".
标签 “God bless”。
Making fun of my, uh,
patented hashtag?
取笑我的，呃，专利标签？
Okay.
好。
Get in there. Because those jorts
were made for walking.
进去。因为那些 jorts 是为走路而设计的。
[Murr] Alright, Sally. If he
let's you post that photo, you win.
[喃喃自语]好的，莎莉。如果他让你发布那张照片，你就赢了。
And if he doesn't, you put
up a bad selfie.
如果他没有，你就会拍一张糟糕的自拍。
[Murr] He we go.
[喃喃自语]他我们走。
Are you on instagram?
-Yeah.
你在 Instagram 上吗？-是的。
Cool. Can I tag you?
凉。我可以标记您吗？
Why? -I-I-was... I had a picture
I was going to post.
为什么？-我-我-曾经......我有一张照片要发布。
I took of you.
我带走了你。
And then I was going to put, uh...
然后我打算放，呃......
"Jorts for days"
[Sal laughs weakly]
“好几天都笑了” [Sal 虚弱地笑]
And then it's #WhoWearsJortJorts
然后是 #WhoWearsJortJorts
#HeWearsJortJorts
#GodBless
What you're uh, what's your name?
你是什么，呃，你叫什么名字？
Minister...
部长。。。
Minister! Minister!
-He's a minister?
部长！部长！- 他是部长？
You're a minister?
-Yeah.
您是部长？-是的。
Ah, swee... God bless! I didn't
even know! I put "God bless".
啊，哎呀......上帝保佑！我什至不知道！我写了 “God bless”。
[commotion]
[骚动]
I screwed it up! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
我搞砸了！对不起！对不起！
Dude!
纨绔子弟！
[Q] Oh, come on!
[Q] 哦，来吧！
[Murr] That's from Coming to America.
[喃喃自语]那是来自 Coming to America。
You see that?
-Sweet, yeah.
你看到了吗？-甜蜜的，是的。
I kinda knew... I kinda...
What are the odds of that?
我有点知道......我有点......那种可能性有多大？
This is... that's crazy.
这是。。。这太疯狂了。
And... share.
和。。。共享。
That's so cool of you.
-Yeah.
你真是太酷了。-是的。
Good sport, too. I like it.
-You live here in New York?
运动也不错。我喜欢。-你住在纽约吗？
"You're a good sport-sport"
“你是一项出色的运动”
You're a good... you're
a good "sport sport".
你是个好......你是一个很好的“运动”。
God bless.
上帝保佑。
[Joe laughing] You got
him mid-yawn!
[乔笑]你让他打哈欠了！
[quietly] This photo is the worst.
[悄悄地]这张照片是最差的。
Open Instagram.
打开 Instagram。
"If a walnut and a horse
had a baby"
“如果核桃和马生了孩子”
[Murr quietly] Oh my
god, there's no way.
[小声喃喃自语]哦，天哪，这不可能。
Hashtag cargo shorts.
Hashtag 工装短裤。
[Joe] He's about to giddy-up.
Get over there.
[乔]他快要头晕目眩了。到那边去。
You mind if I ask you a question?
你介意我问你一个问题吗？
Go for it.
去做吧。
I, um... what's your Instagram?
Do you have an Instagram handle?
我，嗯......你的 Instagram 是什么？你有 Instagram 用户名吗？
That's a weird way
to come in!
这是一种奇怪的进来方式！
I, uh, snapped a photo
我，呃，拍了一张照片
and I thought it'd be funny...
我觉得这会很有趣......
...funny. I snapped the photo.
...有趣。我拍了照片。
This is funny. I think it's a
cute and adorable photo.
这很有趣。我觉得这是一张可爱可爱的照片。
[awkward silence]
[尴尬的沉默]
Well, this just got
a lot weirder.
嗯，这变得更奇怪了。
I was going to [stammers]
我本来要 [结结巴巴的]
If a walnut and
a horse had a baby
如果一个核桃和一匹马生了孩子
as the caption. #CargoShorts
作为标题。#CargoShorts
I love cargo shorts.
我喜欢工装短裤。
I love walnuts and
[stifling a laugh] horses.
我喜欢核桃和 [忍不住笑] 马。
Now it sounds like he's
weirdly hitting on him.
现在听起来他很奇怪地打他。
I think, uh, you know.
我想，呃，你知道的。
You got the... two cheeks.
你得到了...两颊。
You know [mumbling]
it's actually a cute photo
你知道 [喃喃自语] 这其实是一张可爱的照片
I think it's a cu...
adorable photo.
我认为这是一个 cu...可爱的照片。
Stop calling him
cute and adorable!
别再叫他可爱了！
So, you think I should
post it, or no?
所以，你认为我应该发布它，还是不？
No.
不。
No, okay.
不，好的。
[Joe] Alright, Murr. Now
put up a bad selfie.
[乔]好吧，Murr。现在放一张糟糕的自拍。
Now, unfortunately...
现在，不幸的是......
take a very embarrassing
selfie of myself.
拍一张非常尴尬的自拍。
The worst possible selfie
I can think of is this.
我能想到的最糟糕的自拍就是这个。
[Q and Sal] Wow!
[Q 和 Sal]哇！
That a boy, Murr.
那个男孩，穆尔。
We're in this together, my friend.
我们在一起，我的朋友。
Who are you?
你是谁？
Oh, James. Nice
to meet you.
哦，詹姆斯。见到你很高兴。
Oh, there it goes.
哦，好了。
[Joe] Yeah!
[乔]是的！
[Murr] Ready, bud?
[喃喃自语]准备好了吗，伙计？
[camera snaps]
[相机快照]
[Q] Alright, that'll work.
[Q] 好的，那行得通。
[Murr] Now go into Instagram,
upload a photo and type this:
[喃喃自语]现在进入 Instagram，上传照片并输入以下内容：
"Def gots a ####"
“Def 得到了 ####”
[Q] Hashtag cargo shorts.
[Q] Hashtag 工装短裤。
Hey, bud?
嘿，伙计？
I didn't know if you
were on Instagram.
我不知道你是否在 Instagram 上。
Oh, you're not? Because
I-I-I'm-I, uh
哦，你不是吗？因为我-我-我是-我，呃
I do Instagram.
我做 Instagram。
I take pictures of people
in the park. That's you.
我给公园里的人拍照。那就是你。
Okay.
好。
Right there.
-[Q laughing] "That's you"
就在那儿。-[Q 笑] “就是你”
And then I do, I do, like
fun captions
然后我这样做，我这样做，喜欢有趣的字幕
So for this one, I put
"def gots a ####".
所以对于这个，我把 “def gots a ####”放在 “这个 上面。
#CargoShorts
You know, ####?
你知道吗，####？
"What does it mean!"
“这是什么意思！”
You know like... eh...
你知道的......啊。。。
Like a ####.
就像 ####。
Yeah, like a pubic hair
####. Yeah.
是的，就像####。是的。
Now he's got to explain!
现在他必须解释！
So for this one, I put
"def gots a ####".
所以对于这个，我把 “def gots a ####”放在 “这个 上面。
You know like... eh...
like a ####.
你知道的......啊。。。就像 #### 一样。
Yeah, like a pubic hair
####. Yeah.
是的，就像####。是的。
Now he's got to explain!
现在他必须解释！
I can, I can tell because
everybody knows
我可以，我能说出来，因为大家都知道
for me and my followers.
They know I gots a ####.
对我和我的追随者来说。他们知道我得到了 ####。
Like, I thought you were
one of my kindred spirits.
就像，我以为你是我的志同道合者之一。
Oh.
-That def gots a ####.
哦。- 那个 def 得到了 ####。
Yeah.
是的。
Uh, so, I was going to
post that. Is that cool?
呃，所以，我打算发布它。这很酷吗？
Do you not like the picture?
Is that what the issue is?
你不喜欢这张照片吗？这就是问题所在吗？
Got it.
明白了。
What was your name?
-Kieran.
你叫什么名字？-基兰。
Kieran? Joe.
Good to see you, pal.
基兰？乔。很高兴见到你，伙计。
Take care, bud.
小心点，伙计。
It's all tasteful pictures,
though. The whole time.
不过，这些都是有品位的照片。一直以来。
Mostly of the ####.
主要是 ####。
[Q] "My ####"
[Q] “我的 ####”
My ####, specifically.
特别是我的 ####。
Joe. I want you to take a p...
a selfie of your crotch.
乔。我想让你吃点...你的胯部自拍。
[Q] And this is New York City. No one
is even giving him a second glance.
[Q] 这里是纽约市。甚至没有人多看他一眼。
This is why I love living in New
York. Nobody cares.
这就是我喜欢住在纽约的原因。没人在乎。
[Q] I can't wait to see this.
[Q] 我迫不及待地想看到这个。
[Joe] Just get a picture
of this guy.
[乔]就拍张这家伙的照片吧。
[camera snap]
[相机抓拍]
[Joe] Okay, got it.
[乔]好的，明白了。
[Murr] Alright, go on to
Instagram, buddy.
[喃喃自语]好了，继续 Instagram，伙计。
"Hootie let himself go"
“Hootie 放飞自我”
[Murr] Hootie!
[喃喃自语]哎呀！
[Q] Hootie let himself go?
[Q] Hootie 放飞自我？
[Sal laughing] Yeah.
[Sal 笑]是的。
Okay. By the way, my phone
autocorrects "Hootie" to "booty".
好。顺便说一句，我的手机会自动将“Hootie”更正为“booty”。
Tells you about my life.
告诉你我的生活。
[Joe] Yeah we know
what you're texting.
[乔]是的，我们知道你在发什么短信。
Well, you know what?
Either one works.
嗯，你知道吗？任何一个都有效。
[Sal laughing] Okay,
that wasn't too obvious.
[Sal 笑]好吧，这并不太明显。
You put the coffee on
his knee almost.
你几乎把咖啡放在他的膝盖上。
[Murr] The coffee cup is our
microphone. [Joe] Yeah.
[喃喃自语]咖啡杯是我们的麦克风。[乔]是的。
[Joe] Alright, well peace out!
[乔]好了，平安！
Excuse me!
对不起！
Sir! Is this your coffee?
先生！这是你的咖啡吗？
Oh. Would you...
哦。你会...
What's your Instagram?
你的 Instagram 是什么？
Oh. I do.
哦。我愿意。
Because what I do, is I
like to get silly.
因为我所做的，就是我喜欢变得愚蠢。
Right, right.
对，对。
You know what I mean? I take
pictures and I put funny captions.
你知道我的意思？我拍照并放置有趣的标题。
And I saw you
listening to music.
我看到你在听音乐。
And, you know, I
love music.
而且，你知道，我喜欢音乐。
I'm a big Hootie and
the Blowfish fan. -Okay
我是 Hootie and the Blowfish 的忠实粉丝。-好
Anyway, neither here nor there.
无论如何，既不在这里也不在那里。
Uh, I took a picture of you
呃，我给你拍了一张照片
looking at your--your iPhone there
看着你的——你的 iPhone 在那儿
and I wrote, uh,
"Hootie let himself go".
我写道，呃，“Hootie let yourself go”。
Uh, but of course, I would
never put that out without
呃，但当然，如果没有
without your permission,
because
未经您的许可，因为
I respect people's privacy.
我尊重人们的隐私。
Ohh!
哦！
Sweet. Could you hit that share for me?
甜。您能帮我打中那个份额吗？
Oh! Wow!
哦！哇！
I didn't see that one coming.
我没看到那个会来。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢。
No, no problem.
不，没问题。
You want to go get a drink?
你想去喝一杯吗？
Ah, maybe later.
啊，也许以后。
You sure? -Yeah, I'm kinda
waiting for somebody.
你确定？-是的，我有点在等人。
Oh, okay. Really?
-That's why. Yeah.
哦，好吧。真？- 这就是为什么。是的。
Because I Only Wanna
Be With You
因为我只想和你在一起
Joe and Murr couldn't get an upload
Joe 和 Murr 无法上传
so Murr is the #Loser.
所以 Murr 是 #Loser。
Alright, Murr!
好吧，Murr！
Murray is our big loser.
穆雷是我们最大的输家。
That's right. And today
we're at Tumblr,
没错。今天我们来到 Tumblr，
and the CEO is giving
their weekly meeting
首席执行官正在召开他们的每周会议
and Murray, you are
a new hire
Murray，您是新员工
very hip and young
非常时髦和年轻
and you are going to
heckle the whole thing.
而你要对整件事嘲笑。
[Joe] Yes.
-Oh come on.
[乔]是的。-拜托。
Just before we
get rolling here
就在我们开始之前
I would love it
if this week
如果本周
[Sal] The CEO is the only one in the room
that knows. He gave us permission
[萨尔]CEO 是房间里唯一知道的人。他允许我们
to film with Tumblr.
与 Tumblr 一起拍摄。
Murray does not know that.
Murray 不知道这一点。
...intern experience.
...实习经历。
Beyza. Come on up.
贝扎。来吧。
[applause and cheering]
[掌声和欢呼]
[Q] Here we go.
[Q] 我们开始吧。
I'm originally
from Turkey.
我来自土耳其。
And I've been working
on iOS Core team.
我一直在 iOS Core 团队工作。
Yell "like a boss".
大喊“像个老板一样”。
It was amazing,
it was wicked.
这太神奇了，太邪恶了。
I organized everything...
Like a boss!
我把一切都安排好了......像个老板一样！
Yeah!
[cheering and applause]
是的！[欢呼和掌声]
[Joe] Yell "like a boss" again.
[乔]再次大喊“像老板一样”。
More obnoxious though.
Go "bouse".
不过更令人讨厌。去 “bouse”。
I had meetings
with other teams
我与其他团队开会
so it was really great.
所以这真的很棒。
Like a "bouse"!
就像一个“bouse”！
[awkward silence]
[尴尬的沉默]
No claps! No claps this time!
不要鼓掌！这次没有鼓掌！
Before I start anything about
my project, I needed to plan it.
在我开始我的项目之前，我需要计划它。
[laughing] LIKE
[笑]喜欢
A
一个
BOUSE!
嘿嘿！
So, I had iOS experience
before but it was...
所以，我以前有过 iOS 经验，但那是......
Before I start anything about
my project, I needed to plan it.
在我开始我的项目之前，我需要计划它。
[laughing] LIKE
[笑]喜欢
A
一个
BOUSE!
嘿嘿！
So, I had iOS experience
before but it was...
所以，我以前有过 iOS 经验，但那是......
with Objective-C.
与 Objective-C 一起使用。
Um, so I learned...
嗯，所以我学到了......
[yelling] LIKE A BOUSE!
[大喊]就像一个 BOUSE！
[silence]
[沉默]
[Beyza] Um... [laughs] uh...
[贝扎]嗯......[笑]呃......
[Q laughing] Here we go.
[Q笑]来吧。
Uh, I experienced Hack Day.
It was amazing. -[Sal] Yawn.
呃，我体验了 Hack Day。这太神奇了。-[Sal] 打哈欠。
Audibly yawn.
“他打了个哈欠。
..animations, and...
..动画，还有......
[loud yawn]
[大声打哈欠]
[Beyza speaking]
[贝扎说话]
Murr, why don't you take
at least that left shoe off.
Murr，你为什么至少把左边的那只鞋脱掉呢。
Wiggle it around.
摆动它。
[Beyza still speaking]
[贝扎还在说话]
[Q] Oh my god!
[Q] 天哪！
[Sal] Do your thing. Go ahead.
[萨尔]做你自己的事。继续。
Massage your damn feet like you
do when you sit next to us.
像你坐在我们旁边一样按摩你该死的脚。
[Sal] Ew.
[Q] Oh.
[萨尔]呃。[Q] 哦。
This is not normal behavior.
This is what he does.
这不是正常行为。这就是他所做的。
[Sal] Start smelling
your hands.
[萨尔]开始闻你的手。
[Beyza speaking]
[贝扎说话]
[Q] The guy to your left.
[Q] 你左边的那个人。
"You whiffin' that, bro?"
“你闻到那个味道吗，兄弟？”
[Beyza] So, here is other
experiences that I had...
[贝扎]所以，以下是我有过的其他经历......
You whiffin' that, bro?
你闻到那个味道吗，兄弟？
You gots to be whiffin' it.
你得闻一声。
I wasn't expecting
it to be that good.
我没想到它会这么好。
"Is this the girl
that shit herself?"
“这就是那个自己拉屎的女孩吗？”
So, I enjoyed every
moment, and I
所以，我享受每一刻，我
I would like to thank Tumblr.
我要感谢 Tumblr。
Is this the girl that shit herself?
这就是那个自己拉屎的女孩吗？
[applause]
（掌声）
[CEO] Thank you, Beyza!
[首席执行官]谢谢你，Beyza！
"Hey guys, look. It's
Jeff the intern."
“嘿伙计们，看。是实习生 Jeff。
So great having you here.
Thank you.
很高兴你在这里。谢谢。
Hey! There's Jeff the intern!
嘿！实习生 Jeff 来了！
It's Jeff the intern.
是实习生 Jeff。
[Q] No one laughed!
[Q] 没人笑！
[Sal] Oh my god.
[萨尔]哦，我的上帝。
You say something?
你说什么？
[clears throat] Nope.
[清嗓子]不。
[Q] "I thought you
were the intern"
[Q] “我以为你是实习生”
I thought you were
Jeff, the intern.
我以为你是实习生 Jeff。
You're Jeff the "BOUSE"
你是 Jeff the “BOUSE”
Okay.
好。
[Joe] Look at him! He's
shushing him like a toddler.
[乔]看看他！他像个蹒跚学步的孩子一样嘘嘘他。
[Murr] What's that?
[喃喃自语]什么？
Relax, man. It's casual.
放松点，伙计。这很随意。
Just mumble "Tumblr
police" under your breath.
就低声喃喃地说“Tumblr 警察”。
[quietly] Tumblr police.
[悄悄地]Tumblr 警察。
He's so good
at being a dick.
他太擅长当鸡巴了。
Shuqi, come on up.
舒淇，上来吧。
I mean, who doesn't come up?
"Who doesn't come up in this meeting?"
我的意思是，谁不上来呢？“谁不参加这次会议？”
I mean, who doesn't come up?
我的意思是，谁不上来呢？
Seems like the whole
company's coming up.
似乎整个公司都要起来了。
[CEO] Reminder, Briana is on
Slack if you have any...
[首席执行官]提醒一下，Briana 在 Slack 上，如果您有任何...
"Participation trophy
for everybody."
“每个人的参与奖杯。”
It's like a participation trophy.
这就像一个参与奖杯。
Shuqi, tell us about your
experience this summer.
Shuqi，跟我们说说你今年夏天的经历吧。
"Shuqi shook-a now"
“舒淇摇了一摇”
Hello, everyone.
大家好。
Shuqi shook-a now!
舒淇摇了摇——现在！
Hey, I have an idea.
Why don't you zip it
嘿，我有个主意。你为什么不拉上拉链
until he's finished?
Okay? Thanks.
直到他结束？好？谢谢。
[Q] Oooh.
[Sal] Oh my god.
[Q] 噢。[萨尔]哦，我的上帝。
Did you see his face?
He went like this.
你看到他的脸了吗？他就这样走了。
[Q] They're on the IM
calling for security.
[Q] 他们在 IM 上呼吁安全。
[Q] All the employees use
an i-interpersonal IM
[Q] 所有员工都使用 i-interpersonal IM
called Slack. And they're
on it calling for
称为 Slack。他们正在呼吁
security to come get him out.
保安来把他救出来。
So, Murr, just say "I'm on Slack too,
I can see what you guys are doing."
所以，Murr，就说“我也在 Slack 上，我可以看到你们在做什么。
I'm on Slack too. I know
what you guys are doing.
我也在 Slack 上。我知道你们在做什么。
[Joe] He put the phone away!
[乔]他把电话收起来了！
We have a special surprise for you all.
我们有一个特别的惊喜要给大家。
We just found out a
little while ago
我们刚才才发现
how big a fan they
are of Guy Fieri.
他们是多么忠实的 Guy Fieri 粉丝。
It turns out, Joe has
his contact info
事实证明，乔有他的联系信息
and we called Guy
and asked him to call in.
我们打电话给 Guy 并让他打电话。
[cheering and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Is that Guy Fieri?
那是 Guy Fieri 吗？
Hey everybody in Flavortown,
hope you're having a good summer.
嘿，Flavortown 的每个人，希望您度过了一个愉快的夏天。
[cheering]
[欢呼]
Yell "Guy Fieri
you suck"
大喊“Guy Fieri，你很烂”
By the way, you are huge on Tumblr.
I don't know if you knew that or not.
顺便说一句，你在 Tumblr 上很受欢迎。我不知道你是否知道。
Our team really loves you.
a lot. We have a big project...
我们的团队真的很爱您。好多。我们有一个大项目......
Guy Fieri sucks!
Guy Fieri 太烂了！
Hey!
嘿！
[Q] Ooh.
[Sal] Oh my god.
[Q] 哦。[萨尔]哦，我的上帝。
Hey, you better
watch yourself, pal.
嘿，你最好注意自己，伙计。
[cheering]
[欢呼]
[Sal] Oh my god.
[萨尔]哦，我的上帝。
We have a rule here
that says "no assholes"
我们这里有一条规则说“没有混蛋”
and you are at the top
of the "asshole list".
而你就在 “混蛋名单” 的顶部。
Oh!!
哦！！
Wow. -I feel like the
biggest jerk in the world.
哇。- 我觉得自己是世界上最大的混蛋。
Okay, so, Murr has no
social etiquette
好吧，所以，穆尔没有社交礼仪
in this "rough and
Tumblr" punishment.
在这种 “粗暴的 Tumblr” 惩罚中。
And now you get a behind the
scenes look of how it happened
现在，您可以了解它是如何发生的幕后花絮
and bonus footage
from this episode.
以及本集的额外镜头。
I feel like the biggest
jerk in the world.
我觉得自己是世界上最大的混蛋。
I mean, you just told
Guy Fieri he sucks.
我的意思是，你刚刚告诉 Guy Fieri 他很烂。
I know!
-You're such a jerk.
我知道！- 你真是个混蛋。
[squealing] I know!
[尖叫]我知道！
[Guy Fieri] Yo, yo,
what's up "funny man"?
[盖伊·菲耶里]哟，哟，“有趣的家伙”怎么了？
How you doing, Guy? I'm
here with Sal and Brian as well.
你好吗，盖伊？我也和 Sal 和 Brian 一起在这里。
[Q] Hey, bud.
[Q] 嘿，伙计。
So, Guy, we're here. We're
punishing Murray here today at Tumblr.
所以，盖伊，我们来了。我们今天在 Tumblr 上惩罚 Murray。
You are, like, "a thing"
here, so...
你就像是这里的“一个东西”，所以......
when they told us
that, we're like...
当他们告诉我们时，我们就像......
we Facetime with Guy Fieri
and we make Murray
我们与 Guy Fieri 进行 Facetime 通话，我们让 Murray
mess up the Facetime. Like...
搞砸了 Facetime。喜欢。。。
give you a reason to
hang up on him.
给你一个挂断他电话的理由。
That'd be great.
那就太好了。
[Joe] Yeah.
[乔]是的。
Yeah! That's awesome!
是的！太棒了！
Alright, Christine, so you had
to pick out Murr's outfit.
好吧，Christine，所以你得挑选 Murr 的衣服。
-Correct. -Usually the guys
will tell you what to get
-正确。- 通常伙计们会告诉你该买什么
and this time they were just
like "get it" because
而这一次他们就像 “get it” 一样，因为
we have to call Guy Fieri.
我们得打电话给 Guy Fieri。
It's true. We were pressed for
time so I got to make some decisions.
是真的。我们时间紧迫，所以我必须做出一些决定。
[Casey] He kind of looks
good, but for Murr
[凯西]他看起来不错，但对 Murr 来说
like, it doesn't work.
-No.
就像，它不起作用。-不。
It doesn't fit. It's like
a Bizarro Murr.
它不合适。它就像一个奇异的穆尔。
Yeah, it is. It's like a
Twilight Zone Murr.
是的，它是。它就像 Twilight Zone Murr。
Whoa, Joe looks cool.
哇，Joe 看起来很酷。
I know, those glasses
are fancy. -Whoa.
我知道，那些眼镜很花哨。-哇。
Very cool. What are you...?
非常酷。你是干什么的。。。？
Did you dress him?
你给他穿衣服了吗？你给他穿衣服了吗？
I did not dress him. That's
all his credit.
我没有给他穿衣服。这就是他的全部功劳。
Very cool.
非常酷。
[Casey] You hate to... when other
people dress you?
[凯西]你讨厌......当别人给你穿衣服时？
Yeah.
-Because you have a specific style.
是的。-因为你有特定的风格。
This is not my style.
这不是我的风格。
Which is... you're
style is
哪个是......你的风格是
lack of style, right?
缺乏风格，对吧？
Save this outfit. We're going
to use it 10 more times this season.
保存这套衣服。本赛季我们将再使用它 10 次。
Alright, it's the first ever
好吧，这是有史以来第一次
Cyle [kai-ull] Award.
Cyle [kai-ull] 奖。
"Cyle with a C?"
“带 C 的 Cyle？”
Cyle with a C?
带 C 的 Cyle？
Cyle, you can come up.
Cyle，你可以上来。
Weekly installment of Cyle
Cyle 的每周分期付款
"Oh, now I get it. He looks
like Cyle with a C."
“哦，现在我明白了。他看起来像 C 的 Cyle。
Oh, that's Cyle?
哦，那是 Cyle？
This is me. Hi, I'm Cyle.
是我。嗨，我是 Cyle。
You look like a Cyle
with a C.
你看起来像一个带有 C 的 Cyle。
Accidentally kick the seat in front
of you when you cross your legs.
交叉双腿时不小心踢到前面的座位。
[quietly] Sorry.
[悄悄地]不好意思。
[Q] Ooh.
[Sal] Oh my god, oh my god.
[Q] 哦。[萨尔]哦，我的上帝，哦，我的上帝。
Look. Oh my god,
this guy's pissed.
看。哦，天哪，这家伙生气了。
[Joe] This punishment
was made for him.
[乔]这个惩罚是为他准备的。
It's not really so much a
punishment as it's just like
这与其说是一种惩罚，不如说是一种惩罚
he's allowed to
be his true self.
他被允许做真实的自己。
The guys are saying that
that's the real you.
伙计们说，那才是真正的你。
That's not the real
me, Casey.
那不是真正的我，Casey。
How true is it?
-It is not.
这是真的吗？-不是。
[Casey] But there are certain moments
I felt like you felt at home.
[凯西]但有些时候，我觉得你有宾至如归的感觉。
Well, I settled into it.
好吧，我适应了它。
So this is what Murray does
to us every single day
这就是 Murray 每天对我们所做的
and it's annoying
as hell.
这真是令人讨厌。
[Q] Murray, ask if anybody
around you has a napkin.
[Q] Murray，问问你周围有没有餐巾纸。
Got some napkins, bud?
You have a napkin?
有餐巾纸吗，伙计？你有餐巾纸吗？
你有餐巾纸吗？
"Nobody has a goddam napkin?"
“没人有该死的餐巾纸吗？”
Nobody has a goddam napkin?
没人有该死的餐巾纸吗？
How'd you get Guy Fieri?
你是怎么得到 Guy Fieri 的？
[Q] It happened a
half-hour ago.
[Q] 事情发生在半小时前。
[Joe] I know Guy Fieri. I know
Guy. I had him in the pocket for a year.
[乔]我认识 Guy Fieri。我认识盖伊。我把他放在口袋里一年。
[Q] We found out they were big fans here.
-You had Guy Fieri?
[Q] 我们发现他们是这里的忠实粉丝。-你有盖伊·菲耶里（Guy Fieri）？
[overlapping conversation]
And they had the towel already?
-They do that here.
[重叠对话]他们已经有毛巾了？- 他们在这里这样做。
[Q] Wow, I mean they seriously
love Guy Fieri at Tumblr.
[Q] 哇，我是说他们真的很喜欢 Tumblr 的 Guy Fieri。
Every second. Every second gets
you closer to death. Ready?
每一秒。每一秒都让你离死亡更近。准备？
Now we're closer to death.
现在我们离死亡更近了。
Keep this up, you'll get
way closer, way faster.
坚持下去，你会更接近、更快。
[Murr] I'm going to cryogenically
freeze myself.
[喃喃自语]我要把自己冷冻起来。
Is that weird? No.
这很奇怪吗？不。
You're telling me...
You're telling me!
你告诉我......你跟我说的！
150 years ago, the life
150 年前，生活
the average life
expectancy
平均预期寿命
was like 40.
大概 40 岁。
150 years from now,
it's not going to be 110?
150 年后，不会是 110 年吗？
Or more? They're not
going to solve
还是更多？他们不会解决
the diseases that
ravaged humanity
蹂躏人类的疾病
200 years ago are now gone.
200 年前的时代现在已经不复存在。
You just lived another
50 years because of me.
因为我，你又多活了 50 年。
It's just insane to think.
想想真是太疯狂了。
To not cryogenically
freeze yourself?
为了不低温冷冻自己？
Okay, go ahead.
好的，请继续。